▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 决赛
菲斯 6-3 1-6 6-0 蒂亚福 · 赛后捧杯致辞
and Francis, we would love
弗朗西斯，我们想
to hear a few words from you.
听你说几句话。
What's up, Cincinnati?
怎么样，辛辛那提？
What's going on?
大家好吗？
You know, first thing first, obviously,
呃，首先，
I want to congratulate Arthur.
我想恭喜亚瑟。
Hell of a week, brother.
这一周你打得太棒了，兄弟。
First 1000 title.
你的第一个大师赛冠军。
Congrats to you, man.
恭喜你。
And, and your team for sure.
也恭喜你的团队，真的。
And then, of course,
然后，当然，
I got to thank the fans.
我要谢谢现场的球迷。
Y'all all week, man.
这一周你们一直都在，
Seriously emotional stuff.
说真的，太让人感动了。
You guys get behind me so much.
你们这么支持我，
I really appreciate the love.
我真的很感激这份爱。
I go to sleep hearing one, two, three,
我整晚都听着「一、二、三、
foe all week.
Foe」，这一整周都是这样。
So, it's been it's been crazy, man.
太疯狂了，兄弟。
But, thanks again.
但还是要再谢一声。
Shout out Bob Moran.
谢谢鲍勃·莫兰，
One of the best TDs we have in our sport.
这项运动最好的总监之一。
Super player family.
特别为球员着想的一家人，
All about the players.
一切都以球员为先。
It's been awesome to get to know you.
能认识你，真的很开心。
I'm so happy you're running our events
我特别高兴你现在也在管
on the men's side now
男子这边的赛事了，
and not just in Charleston.
不只是查尔斯顿。
Shout out the Navaro family as well.
也要谢谢纳瓦罗一家。
I mean,
我是说，
best arena we have in the game for sure.
巡回赛里最好的场地之一。
It's not even a question.
这一点毫无疑问。
You guys are stand up, Jeff.
你们真的很棒，杰夫。
And then and then of course I want
然后，当然，我还要
to thank my team.
谢谢我的团队。
Mark, Brian, I was going to say Phil.
马克布莱恩，差点叫成菲尔，
Sorry, Rob.
抱歉，罗布。
I got different physios coming all the time.
我这理疗师换得太勤了，
Sorry, bro.
抱歉，兄弟。
Rob, A-Rod, Kenny,
罗布、A-Rod、肯尼、
Zack, who came, Ty, who came,
扎克来了，泰也来了，
ton of friends who came out this week.
这一周来了好多朋友。
So, really appreciate y'all, man.
真的很感谢大家，
It's been a hell of a week.
这一周太疯狂了。
Yeah.
嗯，
I mean, second final we had.
这是我们打进的第二个决赛。
Obviously, I didn't even think I
说实话，我一度以为自己
was going to play this event,
都打不了这站比赛，
so to make a final.
结果还打进了决赛。
We take that and excited to be in New York
这个结果收下了，很期待
in a week.
一周后在纽约的比赛。
And guys,
大家伙，
please keep supporting American T.
也请继续支持美国网球。
Francis, come on over and join me
弗朗西斯，再过来
over here one last time.
跟我一起，最后一次。
Cincinnati. One, two, three.
辛辛那提，一、二、三。
There you go.
就是这样。
All right, let's bring this
好，我们再请出——